# Field Palmer FULL-STACK SOLUTIONS ENGINEER

gfieldpalmer@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/fieldpalmer Denver, CO, 80211

A big-picture thinker with an eye for small details and an extensive record of bringing creative technical solutions from the idea phase to implementation. A specialist in designing, developing, and deploying dynamic, responsive applications that are fun, efficient, and practical.

### Education

#### UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - CHAPEL HILL

- Bachelor of Arts in International Studies, Minor in Geography
   Ski & Snowboard Club, Fishing Club, National Leadership Society
- Professional Certificate, Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp 2018 2019

# **Experience**

<u>2U, Inc.</u> Remote

#### **ACADEMIC ANALYSIS & INSIGHTS LEAD**

2022 - Present

- Automated user analysis to provide nuanced insights into client competencies
- Deliver real-time updates on assessment effectiveness and system efficiency
- Enabled data-driven decision-making using Apps Script and GraphQL
- Implemented time-saving tools and trained team on maintenance

#### SYSTEMS IMPLEMENTATION LEAD

2021 - 2022

- Designed, developed, and maintained multiple web apps using React and Firebase
- Wrote unit tests with JavaScript, Java, and Python to automate code analysis
- Built Node.js and React apps to convert and manipulate CSV and JSON data
- Conducted quality assurance on technical pathway content and data pipelines

#### ACADEMIC DEVELOPMENT ANALYST

2019 - 2021

- Administered technical and pedagogical assessments for IT boot camps
- Delivered specific insights that supported hiring decisions for boot camps
- Provided training on instructional techniques and technical challenges

# Sextant International, LLC

North Carolina | Los Angeles | Slovenia

#### **FOUNDER**

2016 - 2018

- Generated \$150,000+ in revenue marketing products and events
- Established import and distribution network for sustainable, educational brands
- Designed and launched profitable digital marketing strategy for each brand

#### Siman Stones International, Ltd.

Goa, India

#### SALES & MARKETING MANAGER

2015 - 2016

- Structured and executed an international networking ad sales campaign
- Coordinated development and launch of website with external engineering team
- In-house digital marketing efforts led to an 80% increase in annual revenue

## French Ministry of Education & Research

Amiens, France

#### **ENGLISH LANGUAGE ASSISTANT**

2014 - 2015

• Planned and directed over 100 hours of lessons for teenage students in France

• Applied creative techniques to teach grammar and improve conversation skills



## **Portfolio Links**

github.com/fieldpalmer fieldpalmer.github.io

## Relevant Skills

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- React.js
- React Native
- Typescript
- Google Apps Script
- GraphQL APIs
- REST APIs
- MySQL
- Mongo DB
- Firebase
- AWS S3 Storage
- AWS Amplify
- AWS Lamda
- Communication
- Documentation
- Google Analytics
- Zapier Automations
- Bootstrap
- Bash
- Git